Viewers all over the world, right now, begin to rejoice about the healing, deliverance,
breakthrough and freedom that is about to happen.
In His faith, rejoice, right now.
Viewers all over the world, the Bible says:
Come all you that labour, all you that are sick, all you that are poor.
Lord, I have come.
Say after me, viewers, "Lord, I have come.
In Your faith, I have come".
Begin to confess this, right now.
Viewers all over the world,
begin to separate yourself, in the name of Jesus, from that disease,
that disease in your liver - separate yourself!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Heal them, Lord; they have come!
Loose them, Lord!
Heal them from this affliction.
Deliver them from this affliction.
Open your lips; begin to separate yourself.
Break it!
Break the affliction.
Break it, in the name of Jesus!
Prayer.